INIFER PIWONSKI FULL-STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER

JenniferPiwons1 in jenniferpiwonski/ ○ Sunnydayz77

As a public health researcher-turned-software developer, I built my career around patient care and navigating challenging situations. I leverage my patient-centered approach in my software development, providing a detailoriented, analytical, and positive perspective around the applications I build and the teams with which I collaborate.

SKILLS

TECHNICAL SKILLS: React, Javascript, HTML, CSS, Ruby on Rails, Express, NodeJS, Python, SQL, MongoDB, Mongoose, JWT Authentication, Heroku Deployment, MongoDB Atlas Deployment, Surge Deployment, Netlify Deployment, SPSS, NVIVO LANGUAGES: English, Polish, German

PROJECTS

Weather Now App

December 2020

https://github.com/Sunnydayz77/WeatherNow

Weather app that features React Native, a weather API, and GPS location retrieval from your phone

CoPaw App

May 2020

http://copaw.surge.sh/

An internal tool that is a hybrid between an employee directory and a social networking site. Features full CRUD and authentication. This project took second place in the GAxDataDog coding Hackathon in May, 2020

EXPERIENCE

General Assembly

Software Engineering Immersive | Engineering Fellow · January 2020 to April 2020 · New York, NY

Learned full-stack web development in a 12-week full-time training program that exposed me to new frameworks

- Created The +Side, a full-stack positivity blog that alternates between personalized gratitude posts and good news articles. Features full CRUD and authentication. Back-end uses Ruby on Rails and is deployed on Heroku. Front-end uses React and is deployed on Surge
- Created eSwap, a full-stack e-commerce site that allows users to swap items like on eBay. As the team lead on this 4 person project, this web application features full CRUD and has a fully functioning JWT authentication system. Back-end uses Express, Mongoose, and MongoDB and is deployed on Heroku. Front-end uses React and is deployed on Surge
- Created BetterDoc, a web application that details provider information to the user based on name, location, insurances accepted, and provider specialty. Created with React and Better Doctor API. Hosted on Netlify
- Created NutriMate, a nutritional information web application and food journal. Created with HTML, CSS, Vanilla JavaScript, and Nutritionix API. Hosted on Surge

One Medical Group

Administrative Assistant · June 2016 to October 2018 · New York, NY

- Front desk manager of day-to-day operations at a busy primary care office seeing 90 patients a day
- Performed onboarding and trained new team members
- Prioritized patient care needs when triaging urgent care patients, preparing patients for laboratory work, and assisting in billing cases
- Conducted early detection and continuity of care research targeting the health outcomes of potential cancer patients

Albert Einstein College of Medicine

Research Intern · January 2015 to October 2015 · Bronx, NY

- · Worked on a NYS AIDS Institute Expanded HIV Testing Comprehensive Dynamic Trial (EHT-CDT)
- · Conducted a systematic review of literature using NVivo and maintained the database using Endnotes
- · Helped study team integrate key literature findings into the Comparative Effectiveness Matrix tool
- Researched policy incentives for Expanded HIV Testing
- Developed a training program and conference surrounding patient-centered outcomes research (PCOR)

EDUCATION

General Assembly · January 2020 to April 2020 Certificate of Completion, Software Engineering

New York University School of Global Public Health · August 2014 to May 2016 Master of Public Health (MPH), Community and International Health

Colorado School of Public Health · August 2013 to May 2014 Certificate of Completion, Public Health Sciences

Michigan State University · August 2007 to May 2012 Bachelor of Science (BS), Psychology Specialization in Cognitive Science